Metal Cardbot Commentary!
Friends, Not Underlings!
Hey, everyone! Jun here!
Let's watch another episode of Metal Cardbot together!
It's "Metal Cardbot Commentary" time!
Shadow X, setup!
Hey, everyone! It's me again, Shadow X!
Two episodes in a row? Isn't this exciting~!
It's nice to see you again, Shadow X!
Today, let's watch the story of how I
managed to beat Shadow X with a secret weapon!
Shall we get started?
Don't worry. I'll think of a plan starting now.
What are you two talking about?
Vera?
It's none of your business.
Oh, really?
I think it is.
Aah!
Heheh.
Here's the thing.
We were filming a dance video by the docks of Mowtown yesterday.
When robots came out of nowhere and started fighting, I quickly got out my camera.
Ve-Vera is so scary, Jun!
Can't we just reveal the identity of Metal Cardbots to her?
No way, Shadow X!
It'll be dangerous for you if your identity is revealed!
I think Vera is scarier than Blue Cop...
That's true...
I'll have to be more careful next time, so Vera doesn't catch me!
Hey! Get back here!
Good day, everyone.
I would like to address the rumors going around regarding a giant robot.
Giant robot?
Yes!
There have been reported sightings of robots in
concrete channels, under highways, and flying above the city,
Hahaha! What's with that getup, Jun?
Are you playing detective?
You need to get in character to get people's attention!
Your voice is different than usual! It's weird! Heheh!
Doesn't my acting suit the character I'm playing?
But... Who wouldn't be able to tell it’s you, Jun?
Shadow X! In times like this, you just need to suspend disbelief.
That dweeb is trying to sabotage the video we took of the robots!
So tell me, what do we do next?
I'll start thinking about that now.
Not this again!
Jun! It's all set up.
Output 120%!
I'm not backing down yet!
Keep it up, Mega Trucker!
This is sure to work against Shadow X!
Shadow X!
So you guys are training? Should've let me know! I would have helped you!
Augh, this is a rental!
By the way, Jun... what was Edo doing lying on the ground like that?
That was the equipment that Uncle Ed borrowed...
Ah! Is he picking up coins that fell on the ground?
What? No!
He's sad because he can't return the equipment he borrowed!
Hmm, something he borrowed from someone else...
He should've been more careful with it!
Huh?! Shadow X! You're the one who did that!
Woah! Not bad!
Now I'll show you something fun!
Heli-Tornado!
Jun! Are you alright?
I'm okay, don't worry!
Just hang in there. Let's get out of here for now.
Trust me on this! Friends believe in each other.
Friends...
He can't keep that up for long!
His system is overloaded!
Get him now, Blue Cop!
Megabolt Punch!
Megabolt...
Punch!
Aaaaah!
Jun, the power of a friend is amazing, isn't it? Enough to beat my Heli-Tornado!
That's what we call 'friendship'.
So now that I'm friends with Jun, can I become stronger too?
Of course!
Let's get stronger and seal the Metal Cardbots together!
Alright!
Let's show them the power of friendship!
Not an underling. But a friend.
Sealing complete!
Good job.
How was that, everyone?
I finally succeeded in sealing Shadow X!
I hope you look forward to the next "Metal Cardbot Commentary"!